<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Naples Real Estate Video Blog with Vincent Napoleon</title>
    <description>Our mission at Kimberly Vincent Luxury Real Estate Team is to be your best resource for Naples real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Kimberly Vincent Luxury Real Estate Team, your professional Naples Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:39:05 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:39:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Sneak Peek of What’s Happening Now in Our Office</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bzuascWJ3ek?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;What has our team been doing while Vincent is away? See for yourself with this message.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vincent is away right now on a motorcycle trip; and as the saying goes, “While the cat is away, the mice will play.” Our team works hard and plays hard, and so we wanted to take this opportunity to show you what goes on behind-the-scenes at our office. Simply put: There’s never a dull moment around here, but you’ll see what we mean when you check out today’s message. Of course, we always have time for you. So if you ever have any questions about real estate or would like more information about how we can help you meet your goals, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 23:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-sneak-peek-of-whats-happening-now-in-our-office.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-sneak-peek-of-whats-happening-now-in-our-office.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How the Naples Market Has Grown Since Last Summer</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jtXmqIG_DyE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today let’s take a look at how the Naples-area market has changed since last year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s market report for the summer of 2019, we first want to clear up the misconception that summer is a slow time for the Naples market. People tend to believe that nobody buys in the summer and that you can only list your house in the winter months because that’s when everybody is here, but that’s just not true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of July 2019, our agents have had 17,000 appointments to show various properties in the Naples area&lt;/strong&gt;, which is fantastic. To dig even deeper into that, we also found that each buyer averaged 17 showings before making a purchase. Keep that in mind if you haven’t found the right home by your fifth or so home tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For inventory, we had about 5,200 homes on the market in July this year, including condos and single-family homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current list-to-sold ratio in the market is 96%, and our list-to-sales price ratio was 90%. Kimberley and I happen to get an average of 97% of the listing price for our sellers, which is a pretty good market total.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Overall, our market is really on an upswing.%20http://localhost:4000/how-the-naples-market-has-grown-since-last-summer.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Overall, our market is really on an upswing.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In July, we closed 435 single-family home sales and 394 condo sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, sellers added 935 new listings to the market. The interesting part about that is that &lt;strong&gt;even with 935 new listings, the influx of new buyers entering the market meant that we sold all those homes&lt;/strong&gt;—inventory simply could not keep up with all those buyers. Needless to say, buyer activity is super strong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The median sale price for condos in the Naples Beach area increased by 27%, going from $497,000 all the way up to $632,000 in just a year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In July 2018, we had a total of 774 home sales; this year, however, we had 829 sales, which is a 7.1% increase year over year. On a related note, single-family closed sales increased by 14.5% year over year, but closed condo sales remained flat at 394 both this and last July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So overall, our market is really on an upswing. For the most part, pricing really hasn’t changed much except for the high-end condo segment mentioned earlier. Single-family home sales have either remained steady or have gone up, and because of limitations on the amount of land available, many are knocking down old homes and building new ones in their place. &lt;strong&gt;We’re looking forward to a great September market&lt;/strong&gt;, which is typically the slowest month we experience, but we’ve already got a few closings coming up for the month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to buy or sell in the Naples area, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 15:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-the-naples-market-has-grown-since-last-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-the-naples-market-has-grown-since-last-summer.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mayor Bill Barnett Joins Us for an Exclusive Interview</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/W52Ht3rqrrc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Mayor Bill Barnett joins us for an exclusive interview to discuss some exciting upcoming events this month and a few citywide issues you might find interesting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow along in the video above to see our full discussion. We’ve also provided timestamps so you can skip to various sections at your convenience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:04—What’s the status of the Old Naples Hotel?&lt;br /&gt;3:02—Has there been a resolution to the halted project in Crayton Cove?&lt;br /&gt;4:31—What’s happening right now in Naples that the mayor is most excited about? What’s happening that he’s most concerned about?&lt;br /&gt;4:56—A tremendous reconstruction growth spurt, the opening of Baker Park, and the opening of the 8th Street corridor&lt;br /&gt;6:04—A timeline of the 8th Street corridor project&lt;br /&gt;6:49—An update on the gas line project in Aqualane Shores &lt;br /&gt;7:29—Wrapping things up&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about anything we talked about or you have any real estate needs we can take care of, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d love to help you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 10:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mayor-bill-barnett-joins-us-for-an-exclusive-interview.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mayor-bill-barnett-joins-us-for-an-exclusive-interview.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Can Our Concierge Program Do For You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yfmCzaVEfZg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to helping people with their real estate needs, our team is committed to making your buying and selling experiences as smooth and successful as possible. This is why &lt;strong&gt;sellers who list with us have the unique opportunity to take advantage of our exclusive concierge program,&lt;/strong&gt; which we’ll be explaining in greater detail today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we do that, though, we’d like to remind you that even if you’re looking to sell outside of Florida, we have team members all across the nation who would be happy to help you achieve your goals. Better still, you can take advantage of our concierge program even if you’re selling out of state, so long as you do so with one of our agents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re happy to take care of any home improvement that will help you sell quickly and for more money.%20http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-concierge-program-do-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re happy to take care of any home improvement that will help you sell quickly and for more money.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, let’s delve deeper into what the concierge program is and how it can benefit you. In short, &lt;strong&gt;our concierge program lets you easily prepare your home for sale by fronting the cost of home improvement services like staging, painting, and more.&lt;/strong&gt; The best part is that there are no hidden costs or fees. We simply take what you owe out of your closing costs at the end of the deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no real limit to the amount we can spend or the scale of the project we can take on. We can even go so far as to fully furnish a property, as we did recently in the case of one of the new construction homes we’re selling. Whether it’s remodeling, landscaping, upgrading, furnishing, or anything else, we’re happy to take care of any home improvement that will help you sell quickly and for more money. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can see the concierge program in action at one of our recent listings in the video above starting at 2:32.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-concierge-program-do-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-concierge-program-do-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check Out This Great Listing We Just Put Under Contract</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CtvxNUJAZUE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team recently put an incredible property under contract for $5.2 million within just eight days of it being on the market, and we see this as a testament to just how effective our approach to real estate truly is. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, allow us to tell you a little more about this great property. 3215 Crayton Road is a 2-story, 5,700-square foot home with plenty of space and amenities both inside and out. &lt;strong&gt;You can watch a full tour of this fabulous home in today’s video starting at 2:19.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information about how we help buyers and sellers achieve their real estate goals, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 13:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/check-out-this-great-listing-we-just-put-under-contract.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/check-out-this-great-listing-we-just-put-under-contract.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Food for a Great Cause</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3cLKJEEwWIw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Southwest Florida Sizzle is a 14-day, semi-annual, charity-driven event that gives locals (and visitors) the chance to channel their inner foodie and try all the restaurants on their wish list. &lt;strong&gt;This year, the Sizzle will be held from May 30 to June 12&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this fantastic event, every restaurant from Cape Coral all the way to Marco Island and everywhere in between will participate in preparing some excellent lunches and dinners for a great cause. For every lunch or dinner purchased through the program, a dollar of the proceeds goes toward a scholarship fund for the Hospitality program at Florida Gulf Coast University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=For every lunch or dinner purchased through the program, a dollar of the proceeds goes toward a scholarship fund for the Hospitality program at Florida Gulf Coast University%20http://localhost:4000/great-food-for-a-great-cause.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“For every lunch or dinner purchased through the program, a dollar of the proceeds goes toward a scholarship fund for the Hospitality program at Florida Gulf Coast University”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Southwest Florida Sizzle program helps to educate students about the restaurant business&lt;/strong&gt;, and some of the finest restaurants in Naples are then able to hire locally when they graduate from Florida Gulf Coast University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.swflrestaurantweek.com/&quot;&gt;here &lt;/a&gt;to see a list of all the participating restaurants&lt;/strong&gt;; there are almost too many to choose from! Or if you’d like to join us for an outing at one of these great establishments, feel free to give us a call or send an email. We hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 16:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/great-food-for-a-great-cause.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/great-food-for-a-great-cause.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clearing Up a Misconception About Agents’ Roles</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CTtGCi3uT-g?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a buyer is interested in a home, they sometimes think that they’ll only have to deal with the agent who is responsible for that listing. We receive calls all the time from clients who only want to speak with the listing agent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In general, buyers need to be better educated about what each agent’s role in their transaction will be.&lt;/strong&gt; A buyer’s agent is one who works for the buyer, but who gets paid by the seller. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we take a listing, we’re representing the seller’s interest. Our job for them is to get them the highest possible price in the shortest amount of time. But as a buyer’s agent, our job would be to fight to get you the best price, terms, and conditions. Listing agents can’t, therefore, fill both roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You’ll want to speak with someone who is removed from the listing agent, since their job is to represent only the best interests of the seller.%20http://localhost:4000/clearing-up-a-misconception-about-agents-roles.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You’ll want to speak with someone who is removed from the listing agent, since their job is to represent only the best interests of the seller.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agents on either side of a transaction have a somewhat adversarial relationship with each other. That’s why we negotiate separately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So &lt;strong&gt;if you’re on the internet to shop for homes, reach out to us.&lt;/strong&gt; Let us represent you as the buyer, because our job is to get you the lowest possible price, make sure you’re getting the correct inspections, and more. You’ll want to speak with someone who is removed from the listing agent, since their job is to represent only the best interests of the seller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in Naples, we often do represent both sides, but this is doable in a team setting—where one of our agents represents the seller, another can represent the buyer. We would be working as what is called a transaction broker, which is something we’ve done in the case of, for example, a divorced couple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, &lt;strong&gt;if you’re interested in a listing, it’s in your best agent to contact a buyer’s agent before the listing agent.&lt;/strong&gt; That way, you know that you’re speaking to someone with your best interests at heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this or other real estate topics, please feel free to reach out to us. We’d be glad to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/clearing-up-a-misconception-about-agents-roles.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/clearing-up-a-misconception-about-agents-roles.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Great Utilities May Be on Their Way to Aqualane Shores</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FpnLH1hyvns?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aqualane Shores is in the process of voting for the addition of two great new utilities: gas pipelines and high-speed internet. We’re still stuck with Comcast, but many people need better and faster internet. We’ve negotiated a deal with CenturyLink, who will bring high-speed internet to the entire community. In addition, another company will drill gas pipelines underground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Altogether, the cost would amount to around $1.1 million;&lt;/strong&gt; however, the internet and gas companies have agreed to pay for almost all of the costs. In the end, our cost will only be about $300,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This breaks down to $2,693 per single-family home. You can make a one-time payment or have the city of Naples spread it out through your tax bills over four years. If you have a condo, it’d be about $883 altogether. If you have gas already and would just be paying for internet, it’d be $633. &lt;strong&gt;If the vote goes through, they’ll be able to start building by fall.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We have high hopes this will be complete by Christmas.%20http://localhost:4000/some-great-utilities-may-be-on-their-way-to-aqualane-shores.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We have high hopes this will be complete by Christmas.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These developments would help incredibly when it comes to resale value, and they would give the community a huge boost. &lt;strong&gt;They’ll be very beneficial to you as a homeowner both now and in the future. &lt;/strong&gt;Naples Council is going through an extensive approval process that we are hoping to be completed by Christmas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to us. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/some-great-utilities-may-be-on-their-way-to-aqualane-shores.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/some-great-utilities-may-be-on-their-way-to-aqualane-shores.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where Can You Start Your Night on the Town in Naples?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QABs3nkK5J8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of fun things to do here in Naples, and today we just want to share a few local attractions you might enjoy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fans of fine dining will find  so many great restaurants here that they’ll never have to visit the same one twice. This past month, for example, a new Rocco’s Tacos opened in Mercato—we went there recently, and it was fantastic. The intersection at 5th Avenue and 3rd Street, in particular, is a hotspot for some great restaurants. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=There are so many great restaurants here that you’ll never have to visit the same one twice.%20http://localhost:4000/where-can-you-start-your-night-on-the-town-in-naples.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“There are so many great restaurants here that you’ll never have to visit the same one twice.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of places for boaters to go, as well. The Hamilton Harbor Yacht Club is a great private club where you can pull your boat into Bay Front. The Dock and The Boathouse are two other great restaurants in that area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those looking to move to Naples, our team also has a few great new listings coming on the market soon,&lt;/strong&gt; including one in Aqualane Shores that’s right on a canal and one on Gordon Street, which is within walking distance to all those great restaurants on 3rd Street. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about all the great restaurants in our area, I recommend checking out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gulfshorelife.com/2018/05/18/the-26-best-southwest-florida-restaurants/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt; from Gulfshore Life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in our new listings or you have any other questions about our Naples real estate market, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/where-can-you-start-your-night-on-the-town-in-naples.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/where-can-you-start-your-night-on-the-town-in-naples.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Previewing the New-and-Improved Naples Beach Hotel and Golf Club</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lTi5oc3vLwY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you live in Naples or the surrounding area, odds are you’ve been to the Naples Beach Hotel and Golf Club. This resort has been a part of Naples since 1947, and it’s an iconic part of our city. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, though, the Watkins family—the family who had owned the resort since its inception—announced that they were selling the hotel and its surrounding property, including the golf course, to a Phoenix-based development company called The Athens Group, who intended to redevelop it.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because we’re in real estate doesn’t mean we’re pro-growth, but we’re very excited about this ongoing project. The Watkins family interviewed hundreds of potential buyers for this property, and &lt;strong&gt;we believe The Athens Group is the best candidate possible to update it while maintaining the integrity of historic downtown Naples.&lt;/strong&gt; Though they’re based in Phoenix, they’ve done some wonderful projects all across the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If there is any developer who can come to Naples and do the job that should be done, it’s The Athens Group.%20http://localhost:4000/previewing-the-new-and-improved-naples-beach-hotel-and-golf-club.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If there is any developer who can come to Naples and do the job that should be done, it’s The Athens Group.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This resort has been here for a long time, and when you’re facing a beach, some wear and tear is inevitable. As of now, there are 319 units, but The Athens Group plans on reducing that to 220, and their new condos will face both the beach side and the golfing side of the hotel. This reduction means that the hotel will be bought by a high-end luxury player. We don’t know who this player is yet, but we think it will be a Four Seasons. &lt;strong&gt;Along with restoring the hotel, they plan on preserving the golf course in perpetuity.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve spoken to representatives from The Athens Group, and they’re only asking for a couple of building variances, one of which is an 11-foot variance for the ceilings in the condos facing the beach, which we also approve of. On the first floor, they’re building a bowling alley, a kid’s center, and tons of other family-friendly recreational areas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the hotel renovation, the landscaping they’re doing throughout the city of Naples and all along the Gulf Shore Boulevard area is second to none. &lt;strong&gt;If there is any developer who can come to Naples and do the job that should be done, it’s The Athens Group. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about this redevelopment project, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.naplesnews.com/story/money/business/local/2018/11/12/naples-beach-hotel-golf-club-florida-new-look/1975910002/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;click here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this topic or you have any real estate needs that we can take care of, feel free to call or email us at your leisure. We’d be happy to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 11:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/previewing-the-new-and-improved-naples-beach-hotel-and-golf-club.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/previewing-the-new-and-improved-naples-beach-hotel-and-golf-club.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
