<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Naples Real Estate Podcast with Vincent Napoleon</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Napoleon Luxury Real Estate - your professional Naples Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Vincent Napoleon</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-12-11 09:44:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Vincent Napoleon</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Naples, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>vincent.napoleon@gmail.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Vincent Napoleon</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Vincent Napoleon</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Naples, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Naples Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Napoleon Luxury Real Estate - your professional Naples Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Latest Stats from the Naples Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-latest-stats-from-the-naples-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Vincent Napoleon</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-26 16:02:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Vincent+Napoleon/Market+Update.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The spike in inventory we noticed in October is, I think, a direct reflection of the fact that Hurricane Irma struck last September. Since then, we’ve seen a big shift in our market;  numbers have changed dramatically:


  Overall inventory is up 20%. We have 5,990 homes currently on the market. 
  Of those homes, there are about 730 currently pending.
  Our days on market is down to 93 days, an 11% drop. This is good news for sellers. 
  For October, we saw 674 overall closed sales. Of those, 366 are single-family homes, and the rest are condominium sales.
  The median average price of closed sales is about $344,000.


Historically in our market, inventory typically spikes in October because most sellers are preparing for what we consider the height of our season, which is right around Thanksgiving. Right after that time is when the most home sales are done, making it a prime time for sellers in Naples. At that point, we’re inundated with the most visitors we’ll have throughout the year.

I do, however, see an oversupply of homes, which are basically spec homes (brand-new homes that are completed before they’re sold). The spec home market is geographically specific to the area west of U.S. Route 41 (the Tamiami Trail), which is closest to the Gulf of Mexico. A number of various areas here contain spec homes, including Olde Naples, Aqualane Shore, Port Royal,  and the Moorings in Park Shore and Pelican Bay. The great news is that that market is a $2 million-and-above market. We’ve seen a huge 36% increase in sales there.

If you’ve been watching the news, Florida just had an election (like the rest of the country). We now happen to be in the news a little more: Part of our election in Florida included something called Amendment 2, which just passed.

“Now sellers in Florida are protected against unchecked tax increases, and people looking for second homes and investment homes can rejoice.”

Amendment 2’s passing is great news because it caps the amount of tax that is applied to your home for non-homestead individuals. That means for second-homebuyers, third-homebuyers, and others who aren’t full-time residents won’t have to worry about the taxes for that area going up without an end in sight. Now sellers in Florida are protected against unchecked tax increases, and people looking for second homes and investment homes can rejoice.

A really healthy market sits at about 5 to 5.5 months’ worth of homes; we’re currently at 7 to 7.5 months’ worth. As you can see, we’re a little bit higher in terms of inventory. However, some of that is skewed by the fact that there is new development in East Naples and Collier County. Because of that, it would appear we’re moving into a buyer’s market. Now, this can change quickly, as of our year-over-year numbers have gotten significantly better since Hurricane Irma. It took us months to clean up after that, and even today I’m seeing homes that are just now finishing their new roofs and other interior remodeling.

In the end, increasing inventory is good, since it means increased sales.

If you’re looking for an agent who knows the market in our area, I would love to help you out. Reach out to us here at Napoleon Luxury Real Estate or visit our website to search for homes in the area just like the pros do. I look forward to hearing from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Vincent+Napoleon/Market+Update.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Vincent+Napoleon/Market+Update.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The numbers for our local market are finally available, and today we’d like to share the latest updates with you.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Vincent Napoleon</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The numbers for our local market are finally available, and today we’d like to share the latest updates with you.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Naples, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To My Blog!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Vincent Napoleon</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-14 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Our market remains busy, and it’s still an opportune time to command a high price selling your home.  

I know what’s happening in Naples, specifically pertaining to home values, that will directly affect you.

So, I’ll be posting two monthly video messages on this blog to keep you updated. 

They will be valuable and useful in helping you stay on top of what’s happening in the community.

You can also search all homes for sale on the Naples MLS on my website at www.ournaplesflorida.com.

Check back because content will be coming soon!

I’m excited to keep you updated on what’s going on with Naples real estate. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type=""/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>My monthly messages will provide you with market updates, tips, and other educational information having to do with our market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Vincent Napoleon</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>My monthly messages will provide you with market updates, tips, and other educational information having to do with our market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Naples, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Vincent Napoleon</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Vincent Napoleon</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Napoleon Luxury Real Estate - your professional Naples Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
